const level11Questions = [
 {
        question: "Lâu, lâu rồi",
        answers: ["好久 (hǎojiǔ)", "经理 (jīnglǐ)"],
        correct: "好久 (hǎojiǔ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nặng",
        answers: ["重 (zhòng)", "黑 (hēi)"],
        correct: "重 (zhòng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Màu đỏ",
        answers: ["红 (hóng)", "轻 (qīng)"],
        correct: "红 (hóng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nhẹ",
        answers: ["轻 (qīng)", "旧 (jiù)"],
        correct: "轻 (qīng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Cũ",
        answers: ["旧 (jiù)", "药 (yào)"],
        correct: "旧 (jiù)",
    },
    {
        question: "Thuốc",
        answers: ["药 (yào)", "中药 (zhōngyào)"],
        correct: "药 (yào)",
    },
    {
        question: "Thuốc tây",
        answers: ["中药 (zhōngyào)", "西药 (xīyào)"],
        correct: "西药 (xīyào)",
    },
    {
        question: "Lá trà",
        answers: ["茶叶 (cháyè)", "里 (lǐ)"],
        correct: "茶叶 (cháyè)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đồ dùng hằng ngày",
        answers: ["日用品 (rìyòngpǐn)", "件 (jiàn)"],
        correct: "日用品 (rìyòngpǐn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Mưa",
        answers: ["雨 (yǔ)", "把 (bǎ)"],
        correct: "雨 (yǔ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ô, dù",
        answers: ["衣服 (yīfu)", "雨伞 (yǔsǎn)"],
        correct: "雨伞 (yǔsǎn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nước hoa",
        answers: ["瓶 (píng)", "香水 (xiāngshuǐ)"],
        correct: "香水 (xiāngshuǐ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nước",
        answers: ["水 (shuǐ)", "本 (běn)"],
        correct: "水 (shuǐ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đĩa CD/DVD",
        answers: ["光盘 (guāngpán)", "支 (zhī)"],
        correct: "光盘 (guāngpán)",
    },
    {
        question: "Từ điển",
        answers: ["词典 (cídiǎn)", "张 (zhāng)"],
        correct: "词典 (cídiǎn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tạm tạm, bình thường",
        answers: ["马马虎虎 (mǎmǎhūhū)", "最近 (zuìjìn)"],
        correct: "马马虎虎 (mǎmǎhūhū)",
    },
];

export default level11Questions;